Hi, I'm Evan Bates. [music]
>> And I'm Madison Chalk. And we are
three-time Olympians, three-time world
champions, and Olympic gold medalists.
We're participating in USADA's Invest
[music] in Integrity campaign because we
believe in competing with integrity
rather than winning at all costs.
Through this campaign, we can bring
clean sport to the forefront of the 2026
[music]
Winter Games by sharing how and why we
invest in integrity. Clean sport has
always been important to us, but it
really [music] came to life during the
2022 Winter Games when the team medal
ceremony for the figure skating event
was cancelled. Leaving Beijing without
our medals reaffirmed what we already
knew, [music]
that clean sport is paramount and we
need to all work together to ensure a
level playing field for all athletes.
>> Join the movement [music] by sharing why
you invest in integrity.
[music]